## Sukru Oguz Dizdaroglu

Software Developer Marietta, GA 30062 404 429 9328 dizdaroglu105@gmail.com

Highly skilled and motivated software developer over 3 years of experience in .NET, C#, SQL, MVC, and JavaScript. Seeking a challenging position to utilize my technical expertise and contribute to the development of innovative software solutions.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

C#,.Net, Asp.Net ,React.js, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Express.js, Node.js, JSON, MongoDB, MySQL, SQL Mongoose, Sequelize, jQuery, Git, Bootstrap, REST, AJAX, Axios, MVC, OOP, LINQ

## **EXPERIENCE**

**Young Consulting,** Atlanta, GA— *Software Developer May 2021-present* 

- I have worked on .Net ,ASP.NET,MVC and SQL server
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to develop and maintain web applications using .NET, C#, MVC, JavaScript and Jquery.
- Participated in the complete software development life cycle, including requirements gathering, design, development, testing, and deployment.
- I conducted code reviews and ensured adherence to coding standards and best practices.
- Assisted in troubleshooting and resolving software defects and issues.
- Debug essential software components and identify code defects for remediation.
- Assisted Senior Programmer in researching user questions on program processing logic, and calculations as well as performing thorough program and application testing as required
- Implemented features such as validation for uploading files to the client account using LINQ, regex,
- Experience in working Asp.net by developing Controllers, Models, Layouts, Views, Partial Views and HTML, JavaScript, Ajax Jquery, and Css.
- Implemented features Asp.net MVC application.Add Controllers to handle URLs to the Home page of the the site.Add a View to customize the content display along the with its style and also add Model

classes to contain and manage data domain logic. Use View Model pattern to pass information from controller actions to view templates

• Experience on Application Development Using SQL Server Database in Developing Stored Procedure, Views.

**MyLearnMate**, Remote, GA— Web Developer Aug 2020- May 2021

- I have worked on JavaScript, Jquery, Html, Css
- Developed an online math-learning application using HTML, JavaScript, CSS, and Front-End Web Frameworks such as ReactJS
- Implemented authentication, login and authorization features to control access to the portal based on user roles.
- Developed cross-browser/platform HTML5, CSS and JavaScript to match design specs for complex page layouts while adhering to code standards

## **EDUCATION**

**Georgia Institute of Technology,** Atlanta— Certified Full Stack Web Developer – 2020

**Georgian Technical University,** Tbilisi— Electrical Engineer 1992-1997